wonderopolis.org 2019-12-02

# Wonderopolis - Legal & Privacy Notices | Wonderopolis

## Copyright

Content found on the Wonderopolis® website, including the arrangement of content, is exclusive property of the National Center for Families Learning. Under no circumstances may any individual or organization charge for the use of Wonderopolis images, text, programming and materials without prior written permission from the National Center for Families Learning. NCFL reserves complete intellectual property rights to any content downloaded from the website. 

## Trademark

The names, logos, and spirit lines identifying Wonderopolis' images, text, programming (e.g., Wonder of the Day®), and materials are proprietary marks of the National Center for Families Learning (NCFL). Use, reproduction, or modification to any such names, logos, or taglines associated with Wonderopolis is strictly prohibited. Modification to any Wonderopolis identification marks is prohibited. 

## Permissions Policy

Wonderopolis materials may be cited or excerpted in periodicals, books, and educational materials under the following stipulations: 

  * A URL of the material referenced is provided so that readers may access it online
  * Inclusion of the following branding information: “Wonderopolis® is brought to life by the National Center for Families Learning."

Additional requests for permission to feature and use Wonderopolis materials can be faxed to the National Center for Families Learning at 502-584-0172. 

## Disclaimer and Terms of Use

The National Center for Families Learning provides this website to further its mission of inspiring and engaging families in the pursuit of education and learning together. All activities of Wonderopolis further the organization's charitable, tax-exempt purpose. While the National Center for Families Learning makes every effort to present accurate and reliable information on this website, the organization does not endorse, approve, or certify any information on the website, nor does it guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, or timeliness of such information. Use of such information is voluntary. No reference to any commercial product, process, or service implies or constitutes endorsement, recommendation, or preference by the National Center for Families Learning. 

The website is provided on an “As Is" and “As Available" basis. The National Center for Families Learning does not make any warranty as to the accuracy of any images, text, programs, or materials on the website. 

Live links to other websites can be accessed through Wonderopolis. Such external sites contain information created, published, maintained, or otherwise posted by institutions or organizations independent of the National Center for Families Learning (NCFL). NCFL does not endorse, approve, certify, or control these external sites and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, or timeliness of information located at such sites. Use of such information is voluntary. No reference to any commercial product, process, or service implies or constitutes endorsement, recommendation, or preference by the National Center for Families Learning. 

The National Center for Families Learning assumes no responsibility for consequences resulting from use of information contained on the website or from use of the information obtained at linked sites, or in any respect for the content of such information. The National Center for Families Learning is not responsible for, and expressly disclaims all liability for, damages of any kind arising out of use, reference to, reliance on, or performance of such information. 

## Privacy Policy

The National Center for Families Learning respects your privacy. Any information gathered on the site is for the express purpose of determining how families are using the site to further learning together. You may always choose whether to enter any personal information. Any information collected will not be sold, under any circumstances, to any third party. 

The information we collect on our site is only used to recognize you as a Wonder friend and make your experience on Wonderopolis more enjoyable. In most cases, the information we collect on Wonderopolis is non-personal (such as first name only, age, and state). If you submit content that is posted on Wonderopolis, you will be identified on our site only first name, age, and city and state. When we do ask for personal information (such as an email address), it is optional and used only to enable and maintain a safe environment for all learners. We follow Federal regulations and For example, if you submit a Wonder nomination and we know you are under the age of 13, we will ask permission from your parent or guardian to publish any comment you leave about what inspired your Wonder. Without the permission of your parent or guardian, we will only publish your nominated Wonder with no personal information. Your parent or guardian may request to have any personal information corrected or deleted by sending an email to hello@wonderopolis.org. 

The Wonderopolis website includes links to other websites. The National Center for Families Learning is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. You should always read the privacy policy at a website before revealing any personal information. 

## Policy Changes

The National Center for Families Learning reserves the right to make changes to the policies of this website at any time. Any policy updates will apply to everyone using the website and will replace prior policies. 

## Cookie Usage

PASSIVE INFORMATION COLLECTION  
As you navigate through a Web site, certain anonymous information (i.e., that does not personally identify you) can be collected without you actively providing the information. This information includes the type of browser you use, what pages on the site you view and similar technical data. Some of this anonymous data is collected through cookies. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without cookies.
